

# Aung Myo Zaw Backend Developer

Name : Aung Myo Zaw

Address : No.127, Baho Road, Kamayut, Yangon, Myanmar

Mobile : **+959250303166** 

E-mail : aungmyozaw.dev@gmail.com

Date of Birth : 9 June 1992

Gender : Male Marital Status : Married

Profile Link : <a href="https://github.com/aungmyozaw92/">https://github.com/aungmyozaw92/</a>

https://aungmyozaw92.github.io/

LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/aung-myo-zaw-b852a8115

#### **About Me**

I have 7 years of software development experience in delivering high-impact projects and implementing Web Application-based solutions using Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap, Php, Laravel, Ruby On Rails, and Code Igniter

Strong the understanding of Business as well as IT processes and in conceptualizing and driving technical solutions for complex problems with specific expertise in gathering customer needs and rolling out solutions.

#### Work Experience

Dec 2018 - Present

#### **Backend Engineer at Marathon Myanmar**

- Developed and lead a team of 7 to deliver successfully a quality project with a software architect to the client using Microsoft planner and Trello.
- Delivered successfully 5 web applications and 4 mobile applications as backend and lead developer
- Api integrates with E-commerce platforms like Lasan Myanmar, GNC Myanmar, Medicare Myanmar, etc...
- Maintain and support web applications, mobile applications, and API integrations
- Developed backend API using PHP (Laravel Framework) and frontend with Vuejs

May 2017 - Oct 2018

# Software Engineer (Web applications) at Code2LAB

- Developed POS software with 3 team members and a team lead
- Negotiate with the project manager and technical support team to get the best solution of the applications
- Design the database flow and define quick solution
- Developed the application using Ruby On Rails
- Provided support for issues while the project was running
- Provided ad-hoc support request from director
- Delivered successfully POS software as a senior software engineer with the team

May 2014 - April 2017

#### **Web Application Developer at Iklout-It**

- Delivered successfully one project as a web developer for a travel and tour called Myanmar Day Trip (https://www.evercrystal.com/)
- Participated and successfully delivered many projects as web developer under the team leader guideline such as custom CMS system, Invoicing system, Inventory System, STS Transport System, SG Fire Distinguishers Sale & Service System and Portrait Gallery Photo Shooting System, etc...

- Developed with Laravel and CodeIgniter
- Maintained and supported existing applications

# Jan 2014 - April 2014

# Web Developer at Link2Link Technology

- Developed and Designed the link2link website using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Wordpress.
- Maintained and content updated.

#### Jan 2013 - Dec 2013

# Service Technician at F@X Computer Sale and Service

• Maintained and fixed software and hardware issues.

# **Education**

2008 - 2012

# University of Computer Studies, Taungoo - Bachelor in Computer Science

# **Skills**

Html, Css, Bootstrap, Javascript, PHP, CodeIgniter, Laravel, Ruby on Rails

NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB(Mongoose) VueJS, ReactJS

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Git